<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="message_single_screen_migration_all_project_done">All your quiz projects (i.e. %1$d in total) have been successfully migrated. You will now be able to find them in the form of QCM files in your new workspace.</string>
    <string name="message_single_screen_migration_all_project_partially_done">Some of your quiz projects have been successfully migrated to your new workspace; ie a total of %1$d. However, some elements encountered problems during the migration (ie %2$d migration error(s)).</string>
    <string name="message_single_screen_migration_all_project_full_failure">Oops, unfortunately due to an unexpected error none of your quiz projects could be migrated to your new workspace. So a total of %1$d project(s) in all.</string>
    <string name="message_single_screen_migration_you_have_to_migrate_manually">You will have to manually migrate these projects by exporting them in QCM file yourself by returning to your old \'Creations\' space when you wish.</string>
    <string name="title_migrate_projects">Migrate your old projects</string>
    <string name="message_complete_the_migration_process_now">Complete the migration process now in order to found all your unmigrated projects on this new workspace as QCM files ready to be played, shared or edited.</string>
<!--    <string name="title_migration_failed">Migration failed</string>-->
    <string name="message_migration_single_screen_failed">Unable to automatically proceed to your quiz projects migration due to an unexpected error while processing.\n\nAs an alternative to this automatic processing, you can opt-in to first switch back to the dual-screen mode then import each quiz manually as QCM file.</string>
    <plurals name="message_x_projects_waiting_for_migration">
        <item quantity="other">You have currently %1$d projects that are waiting to be migrated to your new workspace.</item>
        <item quantity="one">You have currently %1$d project that is waiting to be migrated to your new workspace.</item>
    </plurals>
</resources>