<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="title_edit_scoring_policy">Edit scoring policy</string>
    <string name="message_edit_scoring_policy_invite">Configure your personalized scoring policy from A to Z and you will see the descriptive text displayed here.</string>
    <string name="txt_mark_policy_config_allow_negative_final_score">Allow negative final score</string>
    <string name="text_add_per_answer">Per good answer</string>
    <string name="text_all_or_nothing">All or nothing</string>
    <string name="txt_mark_policy_config_marks_adding_strategy">Adding points strategy</string>
    <string name="txt_mark_policy_config_cancel_marks_on_mistake">Cancel all earned marks on mistake</string>
    <string name="txt_mark_policy_config_marks_to_add_on_success">Marks to add on success</string>
    <string name="txt_mark_policy_config_marks_to_deduce_on_mistake">Marks to deduce on mistake</string>
    <string name="txt_mark_policy_config_marks_to_apply_on_no_answer">Marks to apply on no answer</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_copy_title">Enter the title of your copy</string>
    <string name="hint_enter_scoring_policy_title">Enter a title for your scoring policy...</string>
    <string name="message_help_scoring_policy_marks_to_add">Amount of points to add when submitting a correct answer. It supports decimal values.</string>
    <string name="message_help_scoring_policy_cancel_on_mistake">Define whether or not for a each question, the earned points should be reset when the player submit a wrong answer among the selected ones</string>
    <string name="message_help_scoring_policy_adding_strategy">Define if the points to allocate in case of success should be added for each correct answer submitted or only in case the player succeed to submit all the correct answers together without any mistake.</string>
    <string name="message_help_scoring_policy_allow_negative_final_score">Define if the scoring strategy allows a final negative score in case the player has multiple points reduced cause of empty or wrong answer</string>
    <string name="message_help_scoring_policy_marks_to_deduce_on_mistake">Amount of points to deduce from the reached score in case of wrong answer. It supports decimal values.</string>
    <string name="message_help_scoring_policy_marks_to_apply_no_answer">Amount of points to apply in case the player doesn\'t submit any answer. It supports decimal values.</string>
    <string name="message_error_out_of_bound_scoring_policy_marks_to_apply_no_answer">This value should be between the amount of points to add on success and the ones to deduce on failure.</string>
    <string name="message_error_out_of_bound_scoring_policy_marks_to_apply_no_answer_details">You can use any integer or decimal value inside this interval.</string>
    <string name="message_warning_configuration_not_compatible_with_allow_negative_final_score">Please, disable this setting first cause there is no negative marking configured on this policy neither in case of mistake nor in case of no answer.</string>
</resources>